- Richard. Hold it. Richard.
what's the matter?
- Okay. What happened?
I'm not selling these skis to my mother.
Please. A more neon sound.
- Mr Ron. I can't be waiting at the whim...
- Remember: to be free...
- Of your attorney.
- To soar like an eagle. To slip
the surly bonds of Earth.
- All right. Thank you.
- Right? That's the feel.
Here we go.
- The guys are tired. You know?
No. If they start losing...
- Well. If the guys are tired...
- Their chops... All right.
- It sounds that way in the ad. My dear.
- All right. They've never
let you down before. Jimmy.
- Cut!
- They've never let you down before.
- Uh. Richard. Listen.
We talked about this yesterday. And
l-I'm not getting the sound
that we. Uh. We're looking for.
Look, we're all tired, but, you know,
we might as well not be recording this...
unless we're gonna get
some punch. Now, maybe...
- My ears are clogged
or something, but, uh, it's a...
- Jimmy. We...
- We agreed on this yesterday.
- Say it. What? What? Tell me.
We've been playing a long time.
Okay? We need a lunch break.
Why don't we just get through
one track. One take...
and then give us
your notes. Okay?
- Okay, but, you know, I want... Hold it.
- We can fix it in the mix.
We can do it in the mix. But l-l-I want
to hear it in the performance too.
- How's it going?
- Just. Just surge.
- No. That's fine. I'll hold.
- I want a... Whee!
- Jimmy!
- Wha... Richard. Iook. At the risk...
It's not the fucking "Leonora Overture."
okay? It's a jingle.
Just let us get
through it once. Okay?
And then we'll have lunch
and then we'll have notes...
and then we'll fix it
in the mix. Okay?
Mom wants you
to come home right now!
She's waiting for you.
- Hi.
If she can stand it, I can.
Play it.
Yes, boss.
I think we should apologize
to Jimmy Schwartz tomorrow.
- Get ready. Pull.
- Sweet.
Pull.
Wish for something expensive.
- Mom.
- Okay.
- Goodbye. Take care of yourself.
- All right. You take care.
Say hi to your mom.
- Nice party. Mrs Parker.
- You're welcome. You're welcome.
- Thanks for coming.
- Good night.
I guess we have
new neighbours. Eh?
Hey. You mind
if I run along with you?
No. Be my guest.
Richard Parker.
Oh. Hey. Eddy Otis.
Where's your beautiful
daughter today?
She's away at school.
She comes home
every other weekend.
- Uh. Whereabouts?
- It's a couple of hours from here.
It's a school for
musically-gifted children.
- Oh. You must be very proud.
- You could say.
Let me guess. You're in
something to do with the arts.
Maybe graphics.
maybe advertising.
No. Definitely advertising.
I'm a composer.
I write jingles for ads.
How'd you guess?
I used to sell insurance.
You get a feel for stuff like that.
What do you do?
I'm not even gonna guess.
- I give financial advice.
- Oh. Like what?
- Okay. Health clubs.
- Good. Huh?
- Lousy. Trust me.
- Oh.
Home security?
- Better?
- Oh. Much better.
He said they didn't know anyone. That they
were lonely. What could I say?
- Do you need these?
- Mmm.
And this.
I know how you feel about neighbours.
but it's only drinks.
- I don't drink.
- Since when?
I thought I was getting fat.
- You didn't notice.
- What? The getting fat
or the not drinking?
...Jamaica for the weekend
scuba diving.
Anyway. On our way to the airport
to come back and move houses...
we get caught up in a riot.
I swear to God. A riot.
It was fascinating. While I'm
so busy protecting my wife...
I don't notice them
stealing all the luggage.
Hence. The outfit when we arrived.
Everything else was packed.
- Have you never been in a riot. Priscilla?
- Sorry I'm late.
I'm Katherine.
but everybody calls me Kay.
Kay. This is Richard Parker
and his lovely wife Priscilla.
The way I look at life. The way I look at it
is this: money is like blood.
It's no big deal.
but if you want to live...
you've gotta have a lot of it pumping
through the system. For example...
most people will never know what it's like
to drive a boat at 100 miles an hour...
or go to Jamaica for the weekend or see
the Grand Canyon from a hot air balloon.
You see what I'm saying?
Without money...
you shrivel up.
So how do you explain all those
shrivelled-up. Rich people?
I'll tell you how.
Because those people...
they know how to make money. But
they don't know how to spend it.
Gettin' money's easy.
We have to talk.
- What would you invest in?
- Myself?
- Yeah.
- Drug and alcohol rehab centres.
I'm serious. It's the number one investment
op of the '90s. Priscilla. People are sheep.
You tell them they can't quit on their own
and suddenly everybody needs help.
I mean. The human mind.
What can you say?
You know what I'd do
if I had some serious money?
Misery
Come on. Help me out here.
Don't put no headstone
on my grave
All my life
I've been a slave
And I don't want
the world to know
Here lies the fool
who loves you so
Free from all this
Misery
Richard.
Come to bed.
You know. Me and Kay were saying.
you two have really got it made:
a nice home. A nice business.
a beautiful. Talented daughter...
a great marriage.
- I'm very lucky.
- What's the trick?
- To which?
- Marriage. How do you hold it
all together?
Trust. I guess.
Trust.
That's very interesting.
You know. I'm planning this trip down
to South Carolina this weekend.
I'm gonna fly down in my plane.
I got some property to check out.
- Why don't you and Priscilla come along?
- You have a plane?
Just a little twin engine Piper.
- Well. I'm sure we'd love to but...
- Look. If money's a problem...
- No. It's not really the money...
- Well. Good. Then we'll have fun.
- It's jus... Uh. Do you think we ought to...
- Now watch this.
Eddy. Careful!
Eddy!
Well. Let's say 5.000.
With 5.000. I'd put one in the bank.
one in bonds and play the stock market
with the rest.
The stock market?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Okay.
How come you never pursued
a singing career?
There's a lot worse voices out there.
I guess Eddy got
all the self-confidence.
Maybe I could help you. That way
I'd get to play some blues. And. Uh...
You know. You...
I would take this wall out.
You know. Take it out. Make this
whole area screened in.
It would open it up a lot and then put
like blue shutters on it or something...
to give it a bit of life.
you know?
It could use it.
- What?
- Nothing. Go ahead.
- I'm being my usual self. Right?
- No. I like it.
I'm gonna take over.
Oh. Never mind.
Come on.
I'm surprised Priscilla hasn't tried
to sell off some of her investments.
She was up to 15.000
last time I went over it.
Fifteen from five?
She has a good head on her shoulders.
What can I tell you?
Squeeze when you come up.
That five was a gift left by an uncle to go
towards a sailboat. Can't touch that.
How much do you owe?
It's not that much. Eddy.
Let's not talk about it.
No. Richard. I'm serious. Maybe
I can be of some help here.
You can't. Believe me.
Is there anything we can't
talk about? Now. Come on.
- You really wanna know?
- Yes.
Current debts. Credit cards.
bank loans. About 25.000.
Is that all? I can get
you that in an afternoon.
How?
Leave it to me. Bubbi.
Three to six weeks. Okay?
- What-What kind of interest
are we talking about?
- No kind of interest.
I don't loan money
to my friends. It's a gift.
Our greatest glory. Dicky boy. Is not in
never falling but in rising every time we fall.
Oh! Do you see? Now you left yourself
open for that one. You deserved it.
Now. Come on. Come on. That's it.
Come on. That's right. Come on.
Come on. That's it. That's it.
That's it. Hit mine. That's it. Come on.
Come on. Keep it in. Keep it in.
All right. Now. Keep it...
Oh. My God!
- Oh. My God. Eddy.
- Call an ambulance.
- Oh. Richard.
- Thank you. Dr Pettering.
- Talk to you tomorrow.
- You know how to reach us.
- Call if you need anything.
I will. Thanks a lot.
Take care.
- Oh. My God.
- Poor guy. I feel terrible.
He didn't look as bad as I thought.
You know. But he...
Didn't he say he was coming
to take us out to dinner?
- Now.
- Okay. Everybody. Five minutes.
- Okay.
- Priscilla?
- Baby. I fudged.
- Could you come here and help me?
Sure. Sure.
What is it?
l-I'd like to get up. I've been lying
in the same position too long.
Okay. Okay. Here.
You grab on to me.
- Okay. Be careful. Please.
- I will. Dear. I will. Now. On three. Okay?
- Okay. Wait.
- Ready? One. Two...
- Up we go.
- Wait. Slow.
Go slow.
- Are you all right? There you go.
- Yeah.
- There you go! Okay. Richard.
- Ow! Ow!
- Ow! Don't touch me. Don't.
- Richard.
Just give me a little air.
I can't move.
Or can I?
- Oh!
- Ah.
Oh. That's-that's
much better. Well...
Well. What's this?
Your insurance company.
Neck and back
scares the shit out of them.
I'm in the business. Pal. It was easy.
I got this pet doctor. It was nothing.
Oh. I'm gonna keep five
if that's okay with you guys.
Yes. Priscilla.
It's true.
It-It was a scam.
And I'm...
I'm terribly. Terribly sorry.
You broke the law. Eddy.
For us?
What are friends for?
Oh. I don't think we can
accept this. We appreciate it.
- We really do.
- I love this woman.
"I don't think we can accept it"?
It's not that we don't
need the money.
Priscilla. Please. Don't insult me.
I did this for you.
For you.
Now. Come on.
I've been wearing
that neck brace for weeks.
What do you say?
I don't know what to say.
But thanks.
Can't sleep?
No.
You think too much.
What about you?
Is Priscilla asleep?
What about Eddy?
No.
He's at the Watkins'. You know.
the people that own the cabins.
Probably trying to buy the place.
Always looking for a deal.
How long you been married?
Thirteen?
Fourteen years.
Have you been faithful
all those years?
Yeah.
What about you?
I guess I'm kind of
old-fashioned that way.
I guess we both are. Huh?
- Baby, yeah
- Lori?
- Hi. Honey. It's Mom.
- I wanna jump in the middle
- Yeah. We're in a bar.
- And wallow around
- And keep on drinkin'till
I feel like I'm drowned
- No. It's very. Very nice.
- Honey. We decided to stay
another night. All right?
- I want a piece of the party
- So if you need anything...
- And party till I see the light
- Go on. Go on.
- I want a piece of the party
- And party till I see the light
- I'm gonna talk to the guy.
and you're gonna do it.
Give 'em hell.
As I reach out to you
Like a child would do
Darling, don't let me down
I love you so
And I guess you know
That I'm too far gone
To turn around
You wanna fuck my wife.
don't you?
- If I give you my heart
- Oh. Don't look so scared. Richard.
It's no big deal.
- Most guys want to fuck my wife.
- Please don't telephone
I've kind of gotten
used to the idea.
- Don't treat me like dirt on the ground
- As it happens...
I'm not entirely immune
to that kind of thought myself.
Give me a break
- For heaven's sake
- I mean. Nobody wants to blow
their marriage. God forbid.
- But God.
- 'Cause I'm too far gone
- For just one night.
- To turn around
- Wouldn't that be sweet?
- I'm too far gone
- You are insane. Eddy. Fucking insane.
- For backing up now
- I'm too far gone
- And so safe.
- To stop
- Let me ask you something.
- I'm flying high
- You ever wake up in
the middle of the night and...
- Like a bird up in the sky
- You know. Just sort of do it?
- Like. Half asleep?
- Darling
- Yeah. Sure.
- Don't let me down
I wonder what
would happen if...
- You and I got up in the middle
of the night. Went next door...
- Don't make it you
- And crept into the other man's bedroom?
- Whatever you do
- Oh, don't turn my life
- Would they know the difference?
Upside down
I think so.
- I need you so
- And would they mind? Richard.
take a look.
- And I guess you know
- They want exactly what we want.
- That I'm too far gone
- In the heat of the moment. They'll love it.
To turn around
- Hey. It's all set.
- I'm too far gone
To turn around
I'll bet you a thousand dollars
we could pull it off.
- Eddy. Come on. Enough with this.
- Enough? Enough?
You say "enough" real quick.
don't you? Are you...
Wait. Wait. Are you sure?
Let me tell you something.
I can't remember when I've liked a guy
as much as I like you.
but the truth of the matter is...
you're a wimp. You think you can
be alive without taking risks.
- There's a lot of different ways...
- No. That... You do.
That's why you end up living
this 50% existence...
when there's 100% waiting
out there to be had.
You're full of fear.
Your life is choked.
You-You write jingles when
you'd rather be doing albums.
You do it for money.
but you're always in debt.
You wanna make love to my wife.
but you're afraid you'll get caught.
This is how you die.
step by step...
these little things
you deny yourself...
this cowardice.
- It's not that.
- No. That is what it is. Who care...
Who cares if we get caught?
Big deal.
Aw. Forget it. You've lost your juice.
It's no big deal. It's your life.
Make a fist.
Too tight?
You really amaze me Richard.
you know. Just when things start
getting interesting around here...
you go cautious on me. Climb
back into your little shell.
And what about Priscilla? Hasn't she
told you how much more alive she feels?
Eddy. Goddam it.
That's enough. Okay?
The subject is closed.
It's not gonna happen.
I hope we can stay friends.
I don't know. You make me feel bad.
You're so judgmental.
I'm not judgmental.
We're just different. Okay?
- You're you and I'm me.
- Oh. That is absolutely right!
I got balls and you don't. I'm a giver
and you're a taker. That's clear.
Well. In this particular case. It's a hell of
a lot easier for you to give than for me. Pal.
I happen to sleep
with my wife.
Boy. When you stick it in...
Fun, fun in the sun
Fun in the sun
- Sounds good.
- Fun, fun in the sun
Fun in the sun
When you deem me worthy...
I'd like to know what happened
between you and Eddy.
Oh. I got it.
All right. Uh. A little
to the left. I think.
Yeah. Perfect!
Is that a beautiful tree
or is that a beautiful tree?
- Think this tree is big enough?
- It's huge.
- What are we gonna sing?
- It's beautiful.
Dashing through the snow
in a one-horse open sleigh
O'er the fields we go
Laughing all the way, ha-ha-ha
Bells on bobtails ring
Making spirits bright
What fun it is to ride and
sing a sleighing song tonight
- Richard. Will you please
tell me what happened...
- Jingle bells, Jingle bells
- Between you and Eddy?
- Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride in
a one-horse open sleigh, hey
- Is it about Kay?
- Jingle bells, Jingle bells, jingle all the way
- Oh, what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh
- Did you sleep with her?
No.
Priscilla. Please.
Don't be jealous.
There's nothing to be jealous of.
I'm not jealous.
God rest ye merry gentlemen
Let nothing you dismay
- Remember Christ our Saviour
was born on Christmas day
- It's just that...
To save us all
from Satan's power
Something went missing
from this marriage...
- Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
Comfort and joy
- And for a while it...
- Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
- Seemed to come back again.
- From God our Heavenly Father
a blessed angel came
- Now...
- And unto certain shepherds
- We never should have taken that money.
Brought tidings to the same
How that in Bethlehem was born
the Son of God by name
Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
Comfort and joy
- We should never have taken that money?
- Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
Now you say something? Now you're
gonna make your moral judgement.
- It's cold tonight. Don't you think?
- Is that what this is all about?
Eddy lacks your moral fibre?
What about gratitude. Richard?
- On the first day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
- He risked his reputation.
- He risked his life for us!
- A partridge in a pear tree
- On the second day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
- No. He may not always...
- Play by the rules.
- Two turtle doves
- But at least he's in the game.
- And a partridge in a pear tree
- On the third day of Christmas
- When was the last time you took a risk?
My true love gave to me
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
And a partridge
in a pear tree
On the fourth day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
Four calling birds
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
and a partridge in a pear tree
On the fifth day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
Five golden rings
Four calling birds
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
and a partridge in a pear tree
On the sixth day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
Six geese a-laying
Five golden rings
Four calling birds
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
and a partridge in a pear tree
On the seventh day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
Seven swans a-swimming
Six geese a-laying
Five golden rings
Four calling birds
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
and a partridge in a pear tree
On the eighth day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
Eight maids a-milking
Seven swans a-swimming
Six geese a-laying
Five golden rings
Four calling birds
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
and a partridge in a pear tree
On the ninth day of Christmas
my true love gave to me
Nine ladies dancing
Eight maids a-milking
Seven swans a-swimming
Six geese a-laying
Five golden rings
Four calling birds
Three French hens
Two turtle doves
and a partridge in a pear tree
- Whoa!
- Holy cow!
It's out of the park!
- Swing. Whoa!
- Oh!
Come on. Richard. I know I'm...
I'm a tough act to follow.
It's the bat.
It must be the bat.
- It's all right.
- It's the bat.
- Go. Go. Go!
- Get her!
- No!
No!
- Hey. Iook at them.
I would like
to propose a toast.
To neighbours...
and friends.
Heaven
I'm in heaven
And my heart beats so
That I can hardly speak
And I seem to find
The happiness I seek
- You okay?
- Fine.
There's coffee.
Priscilla...
The sports.
I love you.
You kids get out of the street.
- What happened?
- You can't go in.
- I'm their best friend.
- You can't go in! Hey!
You! You.
Samples taken from the victim's
body prove you had sex with her
within a half-hour of her death.
Otis claims you had a "obsessive
fixation" on his wife.
And the murder weapon
has your prints on it.
- We played softball that afternoon.
- Yes.
Meanwhile. Otis says that your story
about crossing back and forth...
during the night. Etcetera.
is nonsense.
And says that immediately
after dinner. Around 9.00 p. M...
he departed for Appalachia Lake.
leaving his wife behind.
Now that's a five-hour trip. Luke Watkins
of Watkins Fishing Lodge...
says Otis woke him
at 2.00 a.m. for the keys.
- It's a lie.
- Now the time of death has been
set between 1.00 and 3.00 a.m.
Now if Otis's story is true. The closest
he could have been to his wife...
at the time she was killed was
somewhere in the middle of the
Chattahoochee National Forest.
I'm telling you. It's a lie.
If I were you. I'd consider
some kind of plea.
Otherwise. Unless
we can break Eddy's alibi...
you could be in deep. Deep shit.
Kneel down.
Hands behind your head. Please.
Okay.
Are they treating you okay?
Don't worry about me.
How's Lori?
What do I tell her?
Tell her the truth.
This is a nightmare.
You have to help me understand this.
Richard. Please. Help me.
Please.
I thought it was
what everyone wanted.
It seems like everyone was
pushing me to do it. Even you.
Who was pushing you
to kill her?
Are you insane?
Priscilla. I didn't kill her.
Richard. You just said you...
Mrs Parker. To the best
of your knowledge...
did any other person
other than your husband...
enter your room
the night of the murder?
No. No. Of course not.
That was your story. Richard?
I thought that was something
the papers made up.
You please. You please think
of some other defence. Please!
How could this have happened? How could
you have done this to Lori. Richard?
How could you have done this
to our- Our family?
Richard! Oh. God!
Everyone told me
not to come here today...
but I couldn't let
anyone else do this for me.
I suppose I never was
as strong as I pretended.
And I don't have the strength...
to be both the good wife...
and the good mother.
So I'm going to be
the good mother.
I want to take Lori
away from all of this.
I want my name back.
I want a divorce.
Lori is in hell. Richard.
And I can't save you both.
What this does is define
the financial terms of the divorce...
to the satisfaction
of the bondsman.
Along with your car
and musical instruments...
this pays my initial fee
and secures the bond.
She's being very generous.
acting so fast.
Well. You have 24 hours to remove
whatever personal effects you want
from the house.
The rest will be sold at auction
to pay for your defence.
And don't get into any trouble.
Oh. Jesus.
Who the hell are you?
My name is David Duttonville.
I'm a private investigator.
I. Um...
I'm gonna sit down now.
You scared me.
Door was open. I used to live
next door. I was just...
Yes. I know who you are.
I thought you were
still in the. Uh...
- I made bail.
- Great.
My company.
Duttonville Research...
it's been hired
by three insurance companies...
to investigate a total
$ 1.5 million double indemnity claim...
by Eddy Otis
on his wife. Kay Otis.
In fact. We were hopin' that
you might be able to help us.
$ 1.5 million?
Yes. That's the point.
It is rather a lot to take out
on a would-be lounge singer...
who never earned a cent
in her entire life.
However. There's
no law against it.
She had a policy on him
in the same amount.
Eddy's explanation is...
that they loved
each other so much...
he figured if
either of them got killed...
they'd need
a lot of compensation.
It's a funny attitude.
The world is a funny place.
So he went back in there...
and he beat her to death...
for money.
Just as simple as that.
Isn't that amazing?
I even think he liked her.
You're saying
he killed Kay Otis?
Of course he killed her.
But what a set-up.
The whole thing
just so he could...
$ 1.5 million.
I checked his alibi.
It's gonna hold.
What about the people at the lodge?
I wonder how much he paid them.
Me too.
But who is Eddy?
Where'd he come from?
I was hoping you knew.
He told me he was
a financial advisor.
Great.
Now I know.
I'm on this for a week.
There's a limit to what
one can do in a week.
I need something solid.
You got anything?
Just what I already
told them.
The police know about
the insurance. I suppose?
They're not interested. I think
they feel comfortable with you.
- Comfortable?
- You know what I mean.
They got a good case.
Look. You got my card.
You think of anything.
you give me a call.
Oh. And by the way.
in case you're interested...
when I interviewed Otis.
he was with your spouse.
The grieving widower
comforting the lonely wife.
I'm gonna get going.
Goodbye.
I'm Richard Parker.
Why are you doing this to me?
- Who is it?
- Call the police.
Get my gun.
then call the police.
I've lost my wife...
my child. My home.
I'm facing a death sentence
or life imprisonment.
Call the police.
How do you sleep at night?
Damn it. Woman.
call the police.
Didn't he pay you
enough to kill me?
Richard, uh,
this is George Gordon.
I'm afraid we failed in getting
a further postponement of the trial.
The trial will be
in three weeks.
I do have to say I would advise
you to reconsider your plea.
Thank you.
All my life
I've been a slave
Just put me down
and let me be
Free from all
This misery
Mmm, that was Olivia Kamen with
'Put No Headstone On My Grave..."
a song made famous
by Little Esther Phillips...
at The Blues Connection here
in Five Points, Atlanta. Next...
There you go.
Kay?
Sorry.
What happened
to the contest?
Contest?
There was a blues contest
on the radio.
- I was just listening to it.
- Oh. That was last week.
You must have been
listening to a repeat.
There was a singer.
Olivia Kamen?
Oh. She won. But when we
went out lookin' for her...
to give her the prize. She lit out.
Didn't leave an address or nothin'.
- What does she look like?
Ooh. She looked good!
- All right!
- Yeah!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And thanks to our friend that
we haven't seen in a long time.
- Tip your bartenders and waitresses.
- They're not bad.
And remember. We love you.
We thank you for loving the music.
Drive safe on your way home.
Good night.
- Who loves you so, mm-hmm
- That's her voice.
I'd know it if she was
singing underwater.
So who got killed
that night?
I don't know.
We gotta exhume the body
and get a closer look.
Can't exhume the body. It was cremated.
I checked on the way over.
Besides. Otis is not the only
one who identified the body.
- Someone else?
- A doctor.
- A doctor?
- Yeah.
I'll bet you $ 1.000 if you
call my insurance company...
you will see that same doctor's
name on an insurance claim...
that Eddy made when he faked
an accident involving my car.
You're suggesting that Otis...
- Went out and hired someone...
- Probably.
who resembled Kay. So you
could make love to her...
- And he could then beat her to death.
- Yes.
I'll think about it.
From all the trouble
you've caused me
Okay. Okay.
she's got a nice voice.
- Turn it off before I break down and cry.
- Don't...
- Do you have any other recordings?
- Like what?
Recordings like she made
before she died.
I told you. She didn't record
anything. That's my point.
No. That's my point.
We have no comparison.
A broad in some club in
Five Points sounds like...
some broad who got
snuffed in Huntcliffe...
according to you.
the accused snuffer.
I go into court with a thing like that.
they'll laugh in my face.
And the initials KO.
OK. Olivia Kamen...
Oh. Please. Please.
Mr Parker. I'm an old man.
Does it fall to me at this time
of life to have to explain...
the fundamental principles of the judicial
system to a man of your intelligence?
Evidence. Dear boy.
Evidence.
So find it. You old bastard.
Find it.
Help me up.
- Hi. Dad. Bye. Dad.
- Say. Don't slam the door.
- No fighting. Junior. I mean it.
- Mama.
- You called me.
- Yeah. I thought you'd call me back.
l-I normally don't do
business here at my home.
- What'd you find out?
- Daddy's coming now.
I know he promised.
- Why don't you have a seat?
- Ready or not. Here I come.
- No. No. No. No. You can't. You cheated.
- There's not a trace so far.
But there was a woman disappeared that
night. Similar appearance and everything.
Hi. Honey. Uh. The boys
are waiting for you to play basketball.
Oh. This is. Uh. Richard Parker.
that insurance case...
- Hello. Richard. Mm-hmm.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Uh. We'll be finished here in a minute.
- I'm gonna start dinner.
Sorry to intrude.
But I did find the doctor who
signed that death certificate.
Name's. Uh. Dr Pettering.
He also signed Eddy's injury claim.
Seems he was a promising
young doctor in Chicago...
till he got greedy
and blew himself up.
He's got a scar down
one side of his face.
Yeah. Otherwise
he's real good-lookin'.
A month after the murder...
he and Eddy went
into partnership.
They call it a residential treatment centre
for addictive disorders.
There is a third partner.
A third partner.
Partner in both senses of the word.
Do you catch my drift?
Your wife.
Priscilla.
If Eddy catches you
prowling around his property...
he will have
your bail revoked.
He's got my wife and child.
Do you think... Do any of you feel
qualified to deal with him...
or do we actually bring somebody
else in? Is that a possibility?
Or is it pretty much
a moot point?
- Hello.
- I got your message.
Didn't I tell you not to go
to Charleston, Richard?
Why didn't he kill the real Kay?
It would have been a lot easier.
Maybe they were partners in it.
Maybe he liked her too much.
- But I don't...
- Maybe they're still in touch.
- It's a possibility, I guess.
- It's my last possibility.
- Hey. Sam. How are ya?
- Oh. I'm just fine.
Honey. Don't squeeze
the bread like that.
These are so special.
Mom. Please.
I really want that.
- Hello. Hi. Eddy.
- Priscilla, hi.
- Did you get the samples?
- Yeah. I got them. I'm on my way.
- Want to go out to dinner tonight?
- No. I think we should stay in.
Lori goes back in a few days and. Uh.
she seems a bit upset lately.
So it'd be great if we could. Uh. You know.
spend the night in the house.
- All right. I'll see you in a little while.
- Love you.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Rape!
Richard! Go away!
- Leave me alone. Please!
- Priscilla!
- No!
- Listen to me!
Don't...
Don't hurt me. Please!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- L...
- I want you to play this for Eddy.
It's Kay. She's alive.
It was another one
of Eddy's scams.
This one was for
a million and a half.
Oh. Richard. Oh.
Just play the tape...
for Eddy tonight.
- May I go now?
- You'll play it?
I'll play the tape.
How's Lori?
Can I see her?
Please? Please!
Priscilla?
Where are you staying?
The Carolina Motel.
For how long?
That depends.
Be careful.
Don't put no headstone
on my grave
All my life
I've been a slave
Now tell my mother
not to cry
I'll see her
in the by-and-by
Tell her that
I'm finally free
From all the trouble
you've caused me
Don't put no headstone
On my grave
All my life
I've been a slave
Just put me down
and let me be
Free from all
This misery
I'm sorry.
That sounded
so much like Kay.
It really got to me.
Where did you find that?
I got it in the mail.
It's from Richard.
Oh. That poor. Sick bastard.
What's he trying
to do to us?
He finds some girl
that sounds like Kay.
He records it
and sends it here.
You think you've
started a life...
and you hear something like this
and it just brings it all back!
I'm sorry.
- You got anything?
- Got. Uh. Three Memphis.
- I got a Memphis. Savannahs.
- Savannah here.
- Atlantic City. New York. Chicago.
- Another Savannah.
Savannah. Savannah. Savannah.
Four Savannahs.
The same day that Eddy
heard the tape. Same number.
- Great. Let's give it a call.
- 912-555-3722.
- Here. Give it a try.
- No. You do it. You do it.
- Just ask for Olivia Kamen.
- Scoville Hotel.
- Hello? Hello?
- Hello. Scoville Hotel.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah. Scoville Hotel.
Uh. Can you give me
Olivia Kamen's room?
- Who?
- That's K-a-m-e-n.
One moment.
- What?
- They're ringing her room.
She's there.
- What can I do for you?
- I'm looking for an Olivia Kamen.
- She's down at the Dominion Cafe.
- Where's that?
It's a joint on
East Broad and Bay.
- Could you walk it from here?
- No. But you could.
Once my cup
was overflowing
And I gave
nothin'in return
Now I can't
begin to tell you
What a lesson
I learned
Looking back
Over my deeds
I can see signs
A wise man heeds
But I know
Yes, I know
I'll never
make that same
Mistake again
But I know
Yes, I know
I'll never
make that same
Mistake again
You can't go in there.
Where is she?
Olivia Kamen? Where is she?
- She's gone.
- Olivia Kamen. Which room?
All the way to the top
on the roof.
- I didn't know! I swear...
- Don't lie to me!
I swear. That night
after we played baseball...
he told me to go up to the lake
to Watkins Lodge...
and stay out of sight.
You drove the Mercedes
with the cigarette boat.
The next morning.
he shows up on his motorbike.
We go out on the lake...
and he tells me everything.
And then he said
if I told anyone...
he'd say I'd known all along.
Then I went to Canada.
and I tried to forget...
what I did to you.
Yes?
There's a David Duttonville
downstairs.
He... He wants
to see you alone.
- Hi.
How was Atlanta?
I missed you.
Looks like somebody in your
family's been travelling.
One. Two. Three.
four shirts. One suit.
Tuesday?
And you're sure
it was Richard?
The deskman said he saw him
go upstairs with Miss Kamen.
There were fingerprints
all over the place.
The Savannah police think that by now
there's a good chance
he may have left Savannah.
- Do you want us to put
some men up by the house?
- No. I have a 24-hour guard.
- We have very tight security.
- Do you mind if we just
check around your property...
- To make sure you're adequately
protected?
- No. I'd appreciate that.
- Eddy? Before you come up...
- Yeah?
will you grab my purse. Please?
It's next to the telephone.
Sure.
Thank you.
Hello?
Yes. It is.
What? Now?
Well. It's a little...
All right. Tell him
I'll be over.
Yeah. Five minutes.
Yeah. Okay.
The police are over at the clinic.
They want me to come by.
How are you?
Fine.
You've been through
a lot today.
Don't worry.
I won't be long.
I'm not gonna leave you.
Oh. God.
Did you know that I can
see things. Priscilla?
I can see things nobody can.
I'm so good...
at predicting...
that I can read
tomorrow's headline.
"A man last night broke into
the home of his ex-wife...
"and killed for the third
and last time.
"Arriving tragically too late...
"Eddy Otis. The woman's...
the dead woman's friend...
"shot and killed him.
"The man. Richard Parker.
was already wanted...
in connection
with several other..."
Oh. Yes. He's here.
Priscilla. He's in the house
right now. Wondering...
when he should make
his final move.
Why?
Because I wanted him to.
He's my puppet.
Here he comes.
Come on. Richard.
Come to papa.
Here we are with
the WKPJ traffic news.
Good news for all you happy
commuters wending your way home.
Traffic is flowing smoothly
on all major arteries.
In other news today, an Atlanta court
threw out all charges
against Richard Parker...
in the murder case that shocked
the city earlier this year.
Parker, the court concluded, was set up
by his neighbour, Eddy Otis...
in what veteran insurance investigator
David Duttonville...
called one of the most diabolical
life insurance scams on record.
When asked about his future plans,
Mr Parker said he intends...